Guide to the Papers of Lourdes Portillo, 1979¯2001 M1480
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Audio Visual Materials, 1979¯2001
  - Corpus: A Home Movie for Selena, 1999
    - Tape 204 ¯ 8/17/98 (dubs), 8/1998; 1.0 Items; Video: Dub; Betacam SP; 60 min. (Carton 53, Videotape 10)
    - Tape 205 ¯ 8/17/98 (dubs), 8/1998; 1.0 Items; Video: Dub; Betacam SP; 60 min. (Carton 53, Videotape 11)
    - Corpus ¯ Untitled Version ¯ 10/27/98 (Window Dub), 10/1998; 1.0 Items; Video: Dub; 3/4" Umatic; 60 min. (Carton 53, Videotape 12)
    - Selena "Work In Progress" ¯ Online Output, 10/1998; 1.0 Items; Video: Dub; Betacam SP; 60 min. (Carton 53, Videotape 13)
    - Selena ¯ Hour 16 ¯ Tape 1 of 1 ¯ 8/20/97, 8/1997; 1.0 Items; Video: Dub; Betacam SP; 20 min. (Carton 53, Videotape 14)
    - "Selena Remembers", 9/1998; 1.0 Items; Video: Dub; Betacam SP; 90 min. (Carton 53, Videotape 15)
    - "For Lidia", 9/1998; 1.0 Items; Video: Dub; Betacam SP; 90 min. (Carton 53, Videotape 16)
  - Senoritas Extraviada, 2001
  - Other Projects
    - Cookie ¯ HIV Project: Original 16mm With Marga Gomez as the Angel (2 reels), nd; 2.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Original; ~500 ft., ~800 ft. (Carton 65, Reels 1¯2)
    - Declarations/Derrick Bell/Equality's Child: Original "Equality Child" Beta Tape, 1994; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: BetacamSP; Dub; 20 min (Carton 65, Videotape 3)
    - Immigrant/Walter Mercado: Tape ¯ "Immigrant" Master, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: Digital Betacam; Digital Dub; 32 min (Carton 65, Videotape 4)
    - This Is You Day/Hoy Es Tu Dia: Tape ¯ Rough Cut, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: D¯2 Tape; Dub; 94 min (Carton 65, Videotape 5)
    - This Is You Day/Hoy Es Tu Dia: Tape, 7/1997; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: 3/4" Umatic; Dub; 13 min (Carton 65, Videotape 6)
    - This Is You Day/Hoy Es Tu Dia: Tape: "Hoy Es Tu Dia" & "Immigrants", nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: Digital Betacam; Edited Master; 22 min (Carton 65, Videotape 7)
    - Mexico: January 1993 Tape #15 "Juana/Yucatan", 5/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: BetacamSP; Transfer from Hi¯8; 20 min (Carton 65, Videotape 8)
    - Mexico: December 1993 Tape #16 ¯ Parts B¯E "Sor Juana Scout", 5/1993; 4.0 Videocassettes; Video: BetacamSP; Transfer from Hi¯8; 30 min (E is 20 min) (Carton 65, Videotape 10¯13)
    - Selena: Selena Test, 10/1998; 2.0 Videocassettes; Video: BetacamSP; Dub; 5 min (Carton 65, Videotape 14¯15)
    - Selena: Imagenes Archivo ¯ Max TV Clips, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Dub; 5 min (Carton 65, Videotape 16)
    - Selena: And The End Of The Day ¯ Tape #2, 8/1998; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 60 min (Carton 65, Videotape 17)
    - Selena: Corpus ¯ 35 minute Rough Cut, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Dub; 35 min (Carton 65, Videotape 18)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps: 60 minute version, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: 3/4" Umatic SP; Dub; 60 min (Carton 65, Videotape 19)
    - The Mothers of the Plaza De Mayo: Spanish Version, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: 3/4" umatic; Dub; 67 min (Carton 65, Videotape 20)
    - Tape Cassettes: Tio Oscar ¯ Temp Voiceover, 5/1994; 1.0 Videocassettes; Audio: 1/4" audiocassette; original; 60 min (Carton 65, Videotape 21)
    - Tape Cassettes: Tio Oscar ¯ Narration, 7/1994; 1.0 Videocassettes; Audio: 1/4" audiocassette; original; 60 min (Carton 65, Videotape 22)
    - Tape Cassettes: Ivonne ¯ Part I ¯ 806, 808, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Audio: 1/4" audiocassette; original; 90 min (Carton 65, Videotape 23)
    - Tape Cassettes: Guille & Paula (608); Eva (609) & Maria #1 ¯ Policias, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Audio: 1/4" audiocassette; original; 90 min (Carton 65, Videotape 24)
    - Tape Cassettes: Maria ¯ 4th Trip Part 2, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Audio: 1/4" audiocassette; original; 90 min (Carton 65, Videotape 25)
    - Tape Cassettes: Irma Intr. (611) & Guille ¯ 4th Trip ¯ Part I, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Audio: 1/4" audiocassette; original; 90 min (Carton 65, Videotape 26)